<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">

  <properties>
    <title>Welcome to ActiveQuant 2.o</title>
    <author email="ustaudinger@activequant.com">Ulrich Staudinger</author>
  </properties>

 
  <body>

    <!-- The body of the document contains a number of sections -->
    <section name="Welcome">
<!--    <div align="right" style="display: block; float: right;">
				<iframe width="250" height="400" frameborder="0" scrolling="no"
					marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" allowtransparency="true"
					src="http://activequant.org/html/test.html"></iframe>							
			</div> -->
    <p><strong>SVN TRUNK CONTAINS 2.2-SNAPSHOT (18 JULY 2012). This is bleeding edge, but almost stable at the moment.</strong></p>
    <p><i>Others write "thought leadership" on their flag. We just lead.</i></p>
   	<p>You have reached the landing site of the ActiveQuant securities trading framework. <i><strong>University?</strong> We would be happy to support you and your students on your voyage into quantitative finance! What about a guest lecture?</i> </p>
   	<p>This project is an open source project, but not free software, but it is provided free of charge to academics and hobbyists. You could also say it is an open core software. We provide various commercial services around this open core.</p>
   	<p><strong>RESPECT OUR <a href="license.html">LICENSE</a>.</strong></p> 
	<p>Our people are available for consulting, please contact <a href="mailto:ustaudinger@activequant.com">Ulrich</a> to get in touch with us to make your security trading happen.</p>	
    <p>FOLLOW OUR ATOM/RSS FEED: <a href="http://developers.activequant.org:3000/projects/aq2o/news.atom?key=c3b3aa299eac63a3143dd453d42302ef2090d550">AQ DEV RSS FEED</a></p>
    
    <!-- p><strong>WATCH IT GROW! Have you already seen our FPGA hardware? Check it out.</strong></p>
    <p><a href="http://fpga.activequant.com/"><img src="./images/ad1.png"/></a></p -->
    </section>
	
	
	
	
	

    <section name="Typical use cases">
    <!-- p><img src="./images/comic.gif" align="left" hspace="10"/></p -->
    <p>
	Typical use cases for this project include recording large volume timeseries, managing financial reference data and other information. 
	You can also backtest and run trading systems in production.  
	You might also want to plug in applications written in other languages through 
	a SOAP Service Facade or Matlab to access that data. It is also possible simulate trading, high frequency and low frequency and to move seamlessly from simulation to production through one of the trading venue interface implementations.
	</p>
	<p>
		
		The following diagram shows you briefly, what an <strong>example use case</strong> for the price feed part of ActiveQuant looks like. Notice, YOU GET THIS UP AND RUNNING MUCH QUICKER, IF YOU SIMPLY BOOK US FOR A DAY OR TWO!  
	</p>	
	<p>
		<img src="http://activequant.org/images/aq_gui3.png"/>
	</p>

	</section>
	<section name="How to get started">


	<p>
		We invite you to have a look at our jump start video below that shows you the steps to set up AQ2o 2.1 (2.2-TRUNK is slightly different; currently under development)in your Eclipse IDE, assuming you have the <a href="uberjar.html">AQ Master Server</a>, SVN and Maven up and running.  
		</p>
	<p>
		<iframe width="640" height="360" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/v4UH0-f_pzc" frameborder="0"></iframe>
	</p>
	
	<p>
		Proceed to <a href="./examples/atasteofactivequant.html">our example page</a> for more information.	
	</p>

	

    </section>
    
    <section name="How does the GUI look like?">
    <p>
    Sooner or later, you will want to have a GUI to trade and run things. Here is how it looks like. The GUI is available as a commercial add-on.
    </p>
    <p>
    <img src="./images/aq_gui.png"/>
    </p>
    </section>


    
    <section name="A personal message">
    <p>
    This framework follows the KISS principle as close as possible. In case you wonder why something was done that way and not another, keep KISS in mind. 
	</p><p>
	Another topic, checkstyle. Use it as a hint, but don't take it serious. Things like whitespace warnings and hiding variable names in constructors are something for interns that have nothing else to do. If you have some time, clean things up.   
	</p><p>
	Use this framework in simulation as long as you need to and purchase one of the external interfaces to link it to the real world. Of course you are free to distribute and publish your own external connectors, if you let something flow back to us. Please keep our license in mind.      
    </p>
    
    </section>

  </body>

</document>
	
