<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">

  <properties>
    <title>Welcome to ActiveQuant 2.o</title>
    <author email="ustaudinger@activequant.com">Ulrich Staudinger</author>
  </properties>

 
  <body>

    <!-- The body of the document contains a number of sections -->
    <section name="Welcome">
      <p><img src="./images/pitcher.png" align="right" hspace="10"/></p>
      <p>We put YOU into the driver's seat when it comes to moving your organization forward. </p>
      <p><strong>The AQ MASTER SERVER SOFTWARE is your one-stop-shop for everything financial (and nonfinancial) data.</strong></p>
      <p>Use to <strong>store, retrieve and real-time relay</strong>: 
	  <ul>
	    <li>Instrument reference data, such as tick size, tick value, first and last trading dates</li>
	    <li>Order fills and other order events</li>
	    <li>Clearing account and subaccount values, such as total equity, currency, available margin, used margin</li>
	    <li>Portfolio positions, not only current but also historical</li>
	    <li>Time series data, such as NAV over time, price data, such as bid, ask, OHLC data</li>	    
	  </ul>
	  All out of the box. <strong>With full source code</strong>.	
      </p>      
      <p><strong> Download. Unpack. Run.</strong></p><p><i>In less than 2 minutes*. Promise.</i></p>
      <p> <a href="./two_minutes.html"><img align="top" src="./images/watch_video.png"/></a></p>
      <p><small>* Depending on your internet speed.</small></p>
      <p>Use it as a central storage point and create your processes and applications to generate factsheets or risk reports! </p>
      <p> <a href="http://aq2o.activequant.org"><img align="top" src="./images/banner.png"/></a></p>
    </section>	
    
    
<section name="">
          <p><img src="./images/aq_master_server_interfaces.png" align="left" hspace="10"/></p>
    <p>
      The ActiveQuant Master Server puts you into the driver's seat. Where do you want to go? Where do you want to be in a month?</p>
      
      <p>Plenty of versatile, but easy to use interfaces, integrate the ActiveQuant Master Server into your corporate IT infrastructure. 
      Whether big or small, your organization is going to benefit from cutting-edge technology like several other before. With a proven
      track record of delivering working software, ActiveQuant gives you this tool to see with your own eyes, how easy it come become to 
	store and share data within your network boundaries across a myriad of platforms, tools, operating systems and data sources. </p>
	
    <p> 
	We enable you to pump in data from your own data sources, but we also offer ready-made and extensible connectors for a large variety 
	of world-class data and service providers. We think, there is no need to tell you, how much faster you'll reach your goal. Build on this 
	platform and benefit from decades of software engineering and financial experience. 
      </p>
      <p> Should you ever need custom code - not only for your ActiveQuant Master Server, do not hesitate to contact us - we are here to help!</p>
      
    <!-- /section>

    
    <section name="Technical schema" -->
      
        <p><img src="./images/aq_master_server.png" align="left" hspace="10"/></p>
    <!-- p>
      Data syndication, -aggregation, -transformation: Build it with our server. 
    </p -->  
    </section>

   
    

  </body>

</document>
	
